

Bryan Konowitz

Full Stack Architect & Developer

Las (702) Vegas, 997-Nevada, 3707 US

bryan@kono.sh http://kono.sh

BACKGROUND

GOAL

My goal is to partner with a company that will allow me to employ my passion for development, offer architectural challenges, and expand my knowledge. I truly love to solve complex problems, while keeping user experience at the forefront of my decisions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Architect & Developer, b Spot - Los Angeles, CA Jun, 2013 - Present

- Built an immutable infrastructure and deployment process around integrating Docker, Chef, Consul, AWS EC2 and selfbuilt tooling; took the process of deploying independent services from several hours each, to ~10 - 15 minutes
- Architected and implemented a Ruby and Scala based SOA, utilizing RabbitMQ, Protobuf, and Akka clustering
- Designed and developed a complete authentication and authorization system for security from endpoint through internal services; integrated a multi-prong approach based on being an OAuth2 provider and heavily utilizing the JWT specification
- Developed frameworks for rapid and consistent development of Rails based apis and actor based Scala microservices; utilized the same frameworks for end to end feature implementation
- Provided significant mentoring and pair programming to advance junior and senior developers alike

CTO, Quantus - New York, NY

Jul, 2012 - Jun, 2013

- Architected and prototyped multiple flagship products focused on enterprises; exposing legacy systems as real-time streams (Node.js) & advanced behavior tracking tied to advertising (Scala, Akka, RabbitMQ
- Curated existing client relationships and helped establish new ones to assist in driving the company to its first \$10M in revenue

- Participated in developing and presenting funding pitches for investors and conferences
- Built and managed a team of direct employees and contractors split across consulting contracts and product development

CTO, MGM Resorts International - Las Vegas, NV

Oct, 2011 - Jul, 2012

- Architected a multi-property one-to-one marketing initiative encompassing several dozen customer touch points and numerous disparate backend systems
- Took over and successfully deployed a failing multi-million dollar web development project
- Architected and lead development on a SOA based implementation of mlife.com, a centralized multi-property player rewards system & booking engine
- Lead the development of an integrated customer experience application for replacing multiple simultaneous systems used by reservations agents; built around a custom Coffeescript SPA & a Jersey (Java) REST interface

Senior Enterprise Architect, Pinnacle Entertainment - Las Vegas, NV

Jun, 2010 - Oct, 2011

- Working with a third party creative agency, drove the successful delivery of a new multi-property booking engine, and redevelopment of existing property websites
- Hand-rolled a modern web standards service layer for casino management systems, that passed full penetration testing and security approval by GLI on its first submission (C#, ASP.NET MVC)
- Implemented the first regulatory approved online address change system for a casino company in MO
- Took over implementation and new development of a company wide Campaign Management System; developed features and performed onsite training for marketing department users

Senior Enterprise Architect, ACEP LLC - Las Vegas, NV

Jan, 2009 - Jun, 2010

 Architected the user experience and oversaw development of multiple flagship websites

- Optimized websites for SEO and performance, specifically applying sophisticated scaling techniques during times of national news coverage such as "CNN", "The Today Show", and "Gizmodo"
- Architected and implemented both back and front-end systems relating to an aggregated, multi-property tiered player card system; included development of player kiosk software, storage and message passing systems, player portal website, and internal tooling for reporting and administration
- Designed a data loss prevention (DLP) system utilizing available licensed software to prevent introducing an additional 220,000 license agreement

Consulant, Solved by Code

- Jan, 2009
 - Older contract details are available on request

SKILLS

